<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ocr-digital</string>
    <string name="web_client_d">79123834482-honkqn9ok5te9t1o9sda0dcc4vo8rlr3.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <string name="create_folder_one">Starting from the scan screen</string>
    <string name="create_folder_two">Click the floating action button "new folder"</string>
    <string name="create_folder_three">A dialog box will appear, enter the folder name</string>
    <string name="create_folder_four">Click the create button</string>
    <string name="create_folder_five">The created folder will appear in the scan screen. Folders can also be created inside folders by repeating the steps from inside a folder</string>

    <string name="extract_text_one">Starting from the scan screen</string>
    <string name="extract_text_two">Click the floating action button "scanner"</string>
    <string name="extract_text_three">You will be redirected to the image scanner screen. You can use the camera by clicking the camera button</string>
    <string name="extract_text_four">But you can also select image from the gallery by clicking the upload button</string>
    <string name="extract_text_five">The camera will open up when you choose to click the camera button</string>
    <string name="extract_text_six">After shooting a picture, crop the image to fit the text inside the image</string>
    <string name="extract_text_seven">Wait for the OCR feature to extract the text from the image and redirect you back to the image scanner screen, but now with the extracted text included to the editor</string>
    <string name="extract_text_eight">You can hit the "reset" button to clear the text</string>
    <string name="extract_text_nine">You can save the text by hitting the "check" button</string>
    <string name="extract_text_ten">Upon hitting the "check" button, a menu will pop up to choose which file type to save the text</string>
    <string name="extract_text_eleven">After choosing the desired file type, enter the filename</string>
    <string name="extract_text_twelve">Click the save button and wait for a "File uploaded successfully" message</string>
    <string name="extract_text_thirteen">You can now go back to the home screen and refresh by pulling down on the screen</string>
    <string name="extract_text_fourteen">To view the material, simply click the file</string>

    <string name="translate_one">Starting from the scan screen</string>
    <string name="translate_two">Click the three dots of the file you want to translate. Then click the "Translate" option</string>
    <string name="translate_three">You will be redirected to the Translator Screen where the text of the file is shown. Click the green "Translate" button. Also, you can choose your source and target languages</string>
    <string name="translate_four">Wait for the text to be translated</string>
    <string name="translate_five">Click the "Save" button in the upper right corner and wait for the a message to pop up.</string>
    <string name="translate_six">Go back to the home screen and a new translated file will be saved. The file name will include the original file name and the target language.</string>
    <string name="translate_seven">To view the material, simply click the file</string>

    <string name="home_authenticated">You may now scan your old books or upload your picture to extract the text</string>
    <string name="home_unauthenticated">You may now view the public library of digitized books</string>
</resources>